Lesson 7. Susan hires Bob to run her business. Susan stays up all night thinking about her
cookie business. In the morning she discusses it with Bob. Bob agrees to work for her.
You're up bright and early this morning, Susan. I didn't sleep a wink. I was awake all night
thinking about the new business. Running your own business is lots of work. Are you prepared
to work like a dog? No, but I am prepared to hire you to run the business. You want me to
run a cookie business? Fat chance. Why not? I don't have a clue about making cookies.
I don't even know how to turn the oven on. I'll give you a crash course. Do I have to do
the baking? No. You'll just manage the business side. Needless to say, I have mixed feelings
about working for you. I'll be nice. I promise you'll be a happy camper. Okay, let's give
a shot, boss.